Welcome ! Let's show you some
EasySOA Core & Light features.
First, we are going to explore out
intranet to look for web services.
We just found one of our company's
services. Let's save it to see what we can do.
Note that a few business tags were
extracted from the navigation context.
Our "Pure Air Flowers" service has
just been saved!
Next, we are going to explore another
part of EasySOA Core.
Here is our service registry,
based on Nuxeo.
All of the information that was
collected is stored here.
Now let's browse to our new service.
Most of these metadata can be
overriden, for exemple to store
some documentation.
For technical users, there is also
more technical content you can browse.
New, what about this "Call it" button?
This link lead to this page, when
we can indeed use the service!
This form was automatically generated
to fit the service implementation.
Let's give a try.
Behind the scenes, the service is
proxied, so that the calls are secured.
If you use the service excessively
(here 10 times in 2mn), your won't be
able to call it again before 2 minutes!
Of course, that's just a part of what
EasySOA will be able to do...
Thanks for watching!